{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_6_4W9EUR",
                "player_16_4W9EUR",
                "player_7_4W9EUR",
                "player_10_4W9EUR",
                "player_1_4W9EUR"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                6,
                16,
                7,
                10,
                1
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "pick_up",
                "in_vehicle",
                "stand",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -5749.809,
                    11165.8,
                    199.23,
                    0,
                    -171.7159171771096,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -5135.624,
                    11765.508,
                    208.444,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -5799.506,
                    11233.677,
                    199.059,
                    0.0,
                    -0.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -5201.033,
                    11364.931,
                    199.982,
                    0,
                    148.95609690407662,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -5282.257,
                    10918.873,
                    199.888,
                    0,
                    -169.13199291238246,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "car": {
            "name": [
                "car_3_4W9EUR",
                "car_1_4W9EUR"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                3,
                1
            ],
            "animation": [
                "None",
                "None"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Yellow vehicle with black stripes, modern style, compact structure",
                "White compact car with black grille, sleek design, and four doors"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -5711.805,
                    11376.58,
                    199.151,
                    0,
                    165.37414034602722,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -6291.142,
                    11415.203,
                    199.059,
                    0,
                    174.21629057154212,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "BP_Sedan_child_extras_C",
                "BP_Hatchback_child_extras_C"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -5653.057,
            10993.118,
            199.059
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1129.733059591837
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "car"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -6526.439,
            11681.429,
            207.736,
            0,
            -23.65062380931687,
            0
        ],
        [
            -6006.541,
            10459.579,
            207.959,
            0,
            62.48874037112856,
            0
        ],
        [
            -4465.131,
            10786.836,
            203.504,
            0,
            156.6997781579337,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the_lying_woman_in_black_vest, White_Car or Yellow_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Car",
                    "B. Yellow_Car"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Car"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, Yellow_Car or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or Yellow_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. Yellow_Car"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, Yellow_Car or White_Compact_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Yellow_Car",
                    "B. White_Compact_Car"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Yellow_Car"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants, the_man_in_fedora_hat or Yellow_Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. Yellow_Car"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to Yellow_Car, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a 'crouch' position in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are not wearing glasses in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Excluding any bald individuals, how many people are in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene have light skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding_item",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. reaching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding_item"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. in a car",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. in a car"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the fedora hat relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. To the front of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the fedora hat relative to the man in the burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in the burgundy polo and light pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is man in the burgundy polo relative to the Yellow Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Slightly below and to the left of",
                    "B. Slightly above and to the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "D. Behind"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the Yellow Car relative to the White Compact Car?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the Yellow Car relative to the man in the burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}